[
    {
        "id": "fac8e5d9-5669-4e20-990f-46832ac24c8e",
        "userid": "0",
        "coordinates": {
            "lat": 42.364755900000006,
            "lng": -71.1032591
        },
        "radius": "10",
        "answer": [
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 2,
                "timestamp": 1475441195874
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 0,
                "timestamp": 1475441214026
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 2,
                "timestamp": 1475441233052
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 2,
                "timestamp": 1475465161249
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 1,
                "timestamp": 1475468425915
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 0,
                "timestamp": 1475468467547
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 1,
                "timestamp": 1475476163606
            }
        ],
        "timestamp": 1475441195874
    },
    {
        "id": "12c7c5a5-2fbc-4f85-8303-b53ceb7fb25f",
        "userid": "0",
        "coordinates": {
            "lat": 42.35527753829956,
            "lng": -71.10297918319702
        },
        "radius": "10",
        "answer": [
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 3,
                "timestamp": 1475468615625
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 0,
                "timestamp": 1475468699571
            }
        ],
        "timestamp": 1475468615625
    },
    {
        "id": "7c698b94-a1f4-4fcb-8285-8f108b47a3e8",
        "userid": "0",
        "coordinates": {
            "lat": 42.3554053,
            "lng": -71.1030645
        },
        "radius": "10",
        "answer": [
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 1,
                "timestamp": 1475469185608
            },
            {
                "userid": "0",
                "question": "0",
                "answer": 3,
                "timestamp": 1475469224738
            }
        ],
        "timestamp": 1475469185608
    }
]